

# CONTACT

Address: Bilker Allee 140.

40217 Düsseldorf Phone :+49 1729471513 E-Mail: mano.hicet@gmail.com

# GitHub & LinkedIn

- GitHub URL
- LinkedIn URL

## **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

## Technologies

- Javascript
- HTML5
- CSS3

#### Javascript Frameworks

- React
- jQuery
- Express JS
- Node JS Web Layout

#### Databases

- MongoDB
- MYSOL
- Oracle
- SOL Server

#### Version Control

• Git

## Bootstrap Material UI

# **Programming**

- C++
- Visual Basic
- Power Builder

## LANGUAGES

• Tamil (Mother Tongue) • English : Fluent (C1) • Deutsch: Intermediate

# **PASSIONS**

- Yoga & Meditation
- Mandala Drawing
- Cooking

# MANONMANI SELVAKUMAR

# FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT**

Full Stack Web Developer with hands-on Experience in Teaching Computer Science Technologies who is about to graduate a 1-year Intensive Training in Full stack Web Development (MERN Stack).

Seeking a Internship Position to apply the collected earlier experience and Web Technologies to challenge myself and deliver solution-oriented approaches.

#### **EDUCATION**

Full Stack Web Developer Course| DCI | Since Jul 2020

- During the Course of study, deeply explored the Technologies of MERN Stack and implemented in the Process of Learning through Various Applications.
- Using Material UI and JavaScript Frameworks started designing the Front End for the Final Project.

Deutsch C1 Language Course IIK, Düsseldorf | Oct 2019-Feb 2020 | Sep 2018-Mar 2019 Deutsch B2 Language Course I BBQ, Düsseldorf | Benedict, Düsseldorf | May 2018-Jul 2018 Deutsch B1 Language Course Master of Philosophy(Computer Science)| Bharathiar University, India | 2005-2006 Master of Computer Applications | Bharathiar University, India | 1999-2002 Bachelors in Computer Science | Bharathiar University, India | 1996-1999

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

- ASSISTANT PROFESSOR Swami Vivekananda PG College | Jun 2009 - May 2010 | India
- PROFESSOR Hindusthan College of Engineering & Technology| Jun 2008 - May 2009 | India
- PSG College of Arts & Science | Jan 2003 Nov 2006 | India
- PROGRAMMER ANALYST Tamilnadu Infotech (P) Ltd| Jan 2003 - Nov 2006 | India

Developed a School Automation Desktop Application using PowerBuilder and SQL Server

## PROJECTS DURING WEB DEVELOPMENT COURSE

- Responsive Web Page for a indoor Designs: https://manonmani-s.github.io/la\_villa/
- Simple Bootstrap Theme: https://manonmani-s.github.io/bootstrap\_exercise\_kindness/#